DEAR X
ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES, AND EVENTS
IN THIS WORK ARE FICTITIOUS
CHILD ACTORS WERE FILMED
WITH GUARDIANS PRESENT
I KNOW IT'S DIFFICULT, BUT COULD YOU
TELL ME WHAT HAPPENED BACK THEN?
It was the same as usual.
My mom was yelling at me
to bring her more drinks.
I got smacked a few times, then I got
scared and ran to the bathroom.
Dad.
Can you stop Mommy when she hits me?
She lashes out at me when she's drunk
because you don't do anything.
She's pathetic.
DO YOU REMEMBER
WHAT YOUR DAD WAS DOING AT THE TIME?
How would I stop your mom
when she's drunk and acting crazy?
She threw a total fit, saying
she wouldn't agree to a divorce.
It hurts.
At first, he tried to stop her
whenever she lost her temper.
But after some time,
he just stayed asleep.
Goodbye, my wife.
Don't tell me you threw her.
She got drunk
and fell down the stairs.
I know you're fed up with her, too.
I'll get you a new mom.
She's super rich.
Nothing like our poor family.
Starting now, you do as I say.
Or I will throw you
down the stairs, too.
Help...
Ah Jin.
Call an ambulance.
NAME: BAEK AH JIN
OCCUPATION: ACTRESS
NOTABLE TRAITS:
ANTISOCIAL PERSONALITY DISORDER
FOUND IN ABOUT 4 PERCENT
OF THE POPULATION
SHE IS A SOCIOPATH
SHE VIEWS OTHERS AS TOOLS
AND MANIPULATES OR USES THEM
TO ACHIEVE HER GOALS
SHE HAS DELIBERATELY APPROACHED
ONLY MEN WHO WERE OF USE TO HER
SHE HAS NEVER
PHYSICALLY COMMITTED MURDER
BUT SHE CAUSED THE DEATHS
OF TWO PEOPLE, BAEK AND HEO
SHE STILL HARBORS
AN UNFULFILLED PLAN TO KILL
SHE IS BAEK AH JIN, AN ACTRESS
EPISODE 1: HER X'S
JULY 2016
Hey, it's Ms. Kwak's birthday party.
Let's go! Come on.
- Let's go and have cake.
- Cake? I'm in.
- Come.
- Save me a piece!
Get me a slice, too!
So loud.
How many?
No way.
Did you hear that?
- They're getting married?
- Yes.
- Happy birthday to you
- Happy birthday, dear Ms. Kwak...
- This is Singwang High School.
- Singwang High School.
It was posted anonymously, so...
What are these?
Explain!
- What's going on?
- What are they?
- What's this?
- Is this for real?
- Who's this?
- It can't be true.
What on earth have you been doing?
It's all over the school's website
so we're getting numerous phone calls
from the parents!
You're placed under probation
until it dies down.
We'll contact you
once the situation is resolved.
PRINCIPAL'S OFFICE
Are you all right, Ms. Kwak?
Did you like my gift?
As you always pointed out
I'm an underprivileged child
with no parents or guardians
so I couldn't get you a nice gift.
But I put my heart into this one.
I hope you like it.
Happy birthday.
SIM SUNG HEE, HER X
1. BAEK AH JIN
2. SIM SUNG HEE
Ah Jin and I both got a two-point
question wrong, but why am I second?
There's a one-point difference
in the art practical test.
You two have different ranks,
but you're both in the top grade
so it doesn't affect
the overall outcome.
The art practical test?
What's happening?
Who is Ah Jin with?
Our art teacher?
You haven't gone home yet?
I left my umbrella in the classroom.
I didn't see any umbrellas.
So, someone took my umbrella?
Yes.
Move. Let me look for it.
Come. I'll walk you there
before it's too late.
You're a model student, indeed.
Studying even in the middle
of all this chaos.
But who were you with
in the classroom?
Was it the art teacher who supervised
the evening study yesterday?
You sure have a lot of interest
in other people's business.
But you're also completely oblivious.
You know, people like you
are the first to die in movies.
Good for you, though.
At least in real life, you won't die
for something like that.
I got chills at that moment.
That look on her face.
That tone.
Her true face
that flashed for a split second.
Only I saw it.
Ah Jin, congratulations
on ranking first in the whole school.
And Jun Seo, great job
winning the writing contest.
Jun Seo and Sung Hee, you'll be
preparing for the debate competition
so keep working hard.
I'd like to give my spot
in the debate competition to Ah Jin.
All of a sudden?
Why?
Winning the writing contest
is enough for me to apply early
as a literature-specialized student.
Is that so?
- Have you talked it over with her?
- Yes.
I'd like to participate, if possible.
I'll check the eligibility rules
and let you know.
Good luck with the rest of the day.
- Thank you.
2016 PRESIDENTIAL DEBATE COMPETITION
The debate topic is
the pros and cons
of the death penalty.
As you know, the first part is
a free presentation on the topic
and in the second part
one representative debates
with students from other schools.
You only need to prepare
for Part One.
Yu Bin can help Ah Jin with research.
Ga Yeong, you handle the slides.
I'll write the presentation script.
It's more convenient
when the presenter writes it.
- Sure.
Have you always decided things
this way?
Ah Jin, we also agreed
with her plan, so--
It was the same
in the last idea-pitching contest.
Sung Hee has good leadership
so her way gives us
a better shot at win--
No, she's right.
I've been too assuming.
Ah Jin.
How would you like to do it?
I heard cooperation
among team members
counts for a high portion
of the score.
To score well in that area
isn't it better if we all took part
in Part Two as well?
She has a point.
Then let's think
about how to divide the parts
and decide next time. Sound good?
Okay.
- Hi.
- Bye, guys.
See you!
Good work today.
So annoying.
Are you on your period?
Why the hysteria again?
She kept going on about teamwork
and started showing off
the moment she walked in!
Crazy bitch.
Do you mean Baek Ah Jin,
who pushed you out of first place?
Mom.
Don't worry. I'll take care of it.
I've donated so much to your school
every month as the PTA rep.
You think I can't handle that much?
Can you find out
what tutoring she's getting?
What are you talking about?
Ms. Kwak said she's an orphan
who can't even afford an academy.
Anyway, I have bribed
Ms. Kwak so much money.
But she got fired,
and all that cash went to waste.
Not just money.
She said she needed legal help
so even your dad had to step in.
Who did she get caught
cheating with, anyway?
Are you sick?
You're feverish.
No, I'm fine.
Go on.
It's past eleven. You should go home.
I feel more comfortable here.
Can I borrow your literature notes?
Yes, hold on.
Here.
Jun Seo.
Did Ah Jin ask you
to give up the debate spot?
No, I just thought it didn't suit me.
Still, we're the president
and vice-president.
It'd look better if we went together.
If Ah Jin takes my spot
it will help the team win.
But you're a good writer.
I'm sure you will be
of better help to the team.
Can you say you'll join back?
Let's talk about it later.
She even gave you
something like this?
DEAR JUN SEO
HI, IT'S SUNG HEE
Was that in my bag?
I had no idea.
YOU'VE PROBABLY NOTICED,
BUT I THINK I LIKE YOU
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF ME?
Why are you reading it so seriously?
Just throw it away.
THINK ABOUT IT AND WRITE ME BACK
I'LL BE WAITING!
You should still reply.
I'll do it for you.
Did you hear the rumor this morning?
- About Ah Jin?
- She doesn't have a mom.
That was about Ah Jin, right?
Yes.
Hey, Ah Jin.
Yesterday, Sung Hee told Yu Bin
that you live alone
without your parents.
And she knows
Yu Bin can't keep her mouth shut.
It's not just our class anymore.
The whole school will know.
What are you going to do?
About the debate competition...
There's not much time left.
And we've been getting
complaints from parents
saying it'd be too hard
to align opinions with a new member.
So, the principal decided
only the three original members
should participate.
Which parent
objected to my joining?
This is my dad.
You've seen him on TV, right?
- Yes, I've seen him.
- Right?
And this is my mom.
- Oh, my.
- She's so beautiful.
You look just like her.
- I'm so jealous, Sung Hee.
- It's an article.
- Your family's rich.
- Doesn't she look good?
By the way
do you really have no parents?
Ah Jin!
I'm sorry, sweetie.
I heard you got dropped
from the debate team.
Apparently, Ga Yeong
and Yu Bin's moms were against it.
Are you into Jun Seo?
Did he say that to you?
He asked me to give this to you.
He probably feels bad
doing it himself.
NO ONE LIKES YOU
YOU'RE ANNOYING, SO STOP ACTING UP
Sung Hee.
The homeroom teacher
is looking for you.
We just got a notice
from the competition organizers
that our entire school
is disqualified.
They said someone made a report
and that they didn't want
any controversy.
It looks like
we'll have to drop out this year.
PRESIDENTIAL DEBATE COMPETITION
BRIBERY BETWEEN PARTICIPANTS
AND JUDGES
A PARENT OF A CONTESTANT
FROM SINGWANG HIGH SCHOOL
BRIBED A JUDGE
TO ENSURE THEIR CHILD'S WIN
THE SAME PARENT PAID OFF A TEACHER
TO SECURE THEIR CHILD'S PARTICIPATION
THE STUDENT HAS BEEN ARBITRARILY
REPLACING OR EXCLUDING TEAMMATES...
Damn it.
It has to be her!
Because she was cut off
she spread the rumor
and got all of us disqualified.
Gosh.
Don't worry, Mom.
You know me.
Anyone who's ever crossed me
always paid for it.
I wonder what happens
to those who cross you.
Aren't you the one who spread
the rumor that I'm an orphan?
Thanks. My school life just got
a lot more entertaining.
I heard welfare kids like you
get free rice from the government.
And your tuition fee is free, right?
That rice you eat
is paid for by my dad's taxes.
Thanks.
NO ONE LIKES YOU
YOU'RE ANNOYING, SO STOP ACTING UP
IT CONNOTES FUTILITY...
YOU'RE ANNOYING
CONNOTES
ANNOYING
Fuck, the handwriting's the same.
That bitch.
- HAVEN'T YOU CHECKED THE LEDGER?
- I'M STUDYING FOR THE TEST
- I'LL CHECK AFTER CLASS
- OKAY
Kim Byeong Jin from Class Five
keeps skipping payments.
What do you want me to do?
Follow the manual.
CHINESE CUISINE DOWONJANG
FAST DELIVERY
You.
Stop acting so damn important, okay?
Heard me?
If you piss me off,
you're the one who'll regret it.
You understand?
You're nothing.
So, you're friends with my son?
He and I are
pretty much brothers.
I even...
lent him 250,000 won
of my hard-earned money.
What?
Byeong Jin borrowed money?
Take a look if you doubt me.
It's an IOU.
Apparently, he broke
a friend's headset or something.
Anyway, it's 300,000 won,
including interest.
He was supposed to pay back
5,000 won a day.
But it's so funny.
He vanished after ten days.
You're a student.
You should be studying, not this!
Ma'am.
Just tell me.
Are you paying or not?
The theory that humans are born good.
The four virtues
- of human nature are...
- Jun Seo.
- Forget about the money.
- Jun Seo!
...righteousness, propriety,
and wisdom.
It's a concept that these four
complete a human's moral nature.
Now, the theory
that humans are inherently evil.
It shouldn't be taken to mean
that people stay evil forever.
You were born evil, so you're evil
until the day you die? Not at all.
The philosopher Xunzi argued...
Sorry I'm late.
I'll take her to the nurse's office.
- What happened to her?
- Jun Seo's so cool.
Quiet down.
Gosh, this damn weather.
I swear it's gone insane.
Jeez, how many raindrops
per second is this?
Man, I washed this uniform yesterday.
What is it?
Are you two skipping class?
Why are you soaked?
Did you shower or something?
Looks like you're the one
who got rained on.
I'm sure I told you
not to talk to us at school.
Just go to class
when you're at school.
Who the fuck do you think you are,
telling me what to do?
And you're the one skipping class.
We're not skipping.
We're going to the nurse.
And those AirPods.
Shouldn't you be keeping
those out of sight?
Aren't these expensive?
You swear you won't tell anyone?
Why?
I don't want to get involved
in something that's not my problem.
A model student like you
wouldn't gain anything
from getting involved with me.
You need anything?
If you want something
I can steal one for you.
I don't need stuff.
But I do need a person.
- A person?
- It's a perfect fit for you.
This is good. You'll even get paid.
160,000 WON
BONG SU HUN, CLASS 2-8
BOSS
I'm going home
after I'm done in the nurse's office.
I'll check the ledger tomorrow.
You're not even pretending
to pay attention now?
What's this?
"Touch me and you're dead"?
What's this, Jae Oh?
You punk.
Jeez.
Stop!
You're dead when I catch you!
What just happened?
What is this?
PRESS TO UNLOCK
"Collections"?
I'LL CHECK THE LEDGER TOMORROW
"Ledger"?
What is this about?
Sim Sung Hee?
Why would she do that to you?
Why do you think?
She can't stand seeing me
hang out with you.
Whatever her reason is,
this is too much.
Let's tell the teacher.
Forget it. I'm not a child.
She's been spreading rumors
about me, anyway.
I'll handle it my way.
You should lie down.
Your hair's still wet.
You'll catch a cold.
Jun Seo.
To be honest, I'm scared.
I don't know what she'll do next.
You'll help me, right?
Baek Ah Jin!
Ah Jin, good morning!
Are you feeling okay?
I'm totally fine. Thanks for asking.
Hey.
You didn't hear since you left
early yesterday, right?
It turns out Jae Oh has been running
a loan-sharking scheme with students
and the ethics teacher
caught him yesterday.
And the total amount was huge.
The homeroom teacher yelled so loudly
- that it echoed through the hallway.
- It did.
Is that right?
Hey, there.
I was going to just leave
after five more minutes.
You get the situation, right?
But still
I never said your name.
Now, I don't owe you anything--
Thanks.
I knew you'd do that for me.
Wait.
My ribs.
Did you get hit again?
I honestly don't get it.
Every time you get hit by your father
it makes me angry
because you look so pathetic.
Aren't you sick of living like that?
If it were me, I would find a way
to get away from him.
Not just let him hit you
like an idiot.
I never knew
you were so interested in me.
No wonder.
I knew you were looking at me
in a strange way.
I looked pathetic to you.
Is that it?
I'm only letting him hit me.
Or he'll go and make trouble
somewhere else.
And no matter how useless I am
I can't beat up my own parent.
Yes, you can.
What's so wrong
with protecting yourself?
Jae Oh.
You're not useless.
At least, not to me.
- It's finally lunchtime.
- I was starving!
Can I get one more?
I love grilled patties.
Thank you, ma'am.
Why do you have four patties?
Because the lunch lady loves me.
Right, Ah Jin.
You'll chip in, too, right?
For our teacher's wedding gift.
Of course, I will.
She'll be so happy, right?
Oh, my.
No, you do not pay.
Are you out of your mind?
- What are you doing?
- Sung Hee!
Ah Jin, are you okay?
It splashed everywhere.
I'm fine, guys. I'll head out first.
- Hey, Ah Jin!
- Ah Jin!
So, you're Kim Jae Oh's boss.
You just got caught.
By me.
You really are his boss.
You're the mastermind
behind Kim Jae Oh's scheme.
You act like a perfect student
then shake kids down for cash
behind their backs.
Imagine how happy
the homeroom teacher will be
when she hears the gift was paid for
with dirty money.
Right?
What now?
You'll absolutely hate
coming to school now.
- Hey, stop right there.
- Sung Hee.
Do you have a minute?
What do you want to talk about?
It's about your letter.
You probably know already,
but Ah Jin answered on her own.
I apologize on her behalf.
Sorry.
Save it.
Tell her to say it to my face
if she wants to apologize.
I know you're angry
but I hope you don't get
the wrong idea.
I like you.
What?
What did you just say?
You said you liked me.
I like you, too.
So, are we dating now?
About that.
The people I hate the most
are the ones who cross the line.
I don't want my girlfriend
to be that kind of person.
What do you mean?
I never crossed the line.
Things between you and Ah Jin
have been tense.
As you know, I've been friends
with her for a long time.
If you truly like me
I don't want you to bully her
while we're together.
You're wrong.
We're super close.
Don't worry. I'm not like that.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Good, then.
Are you free this weekend?
How about a movie?
What should we watch?
Whatever you like.
What I like?
I like everything.
It's me.
Who's this?
Who do you think?
Did you already forget my voice?
Kim Jae Oh?
I got a used phone.
Call this number from now on.
Just telling you that.
- I'm hanging up.
- Wait.
Don't hang up.
I need you right now.
How come you mouth off to me
but let others walk all over you?
I think
Sim Sung Hee found out
about the ledger.
Found out what?
Even the fact
that you own the ledger?
And she has your lost phone.
I'll go get it right now.
Don't.
She already sees me
as a thorn in her side.
It's only a matter of time
before the whole school finds out.
They'll talk behind my back
when they see me.
Fuck.
Does Yoon Jun Seo
also know about this?
What is that jerk doing now?
You know how he is.
Even if he stepped up
he couldn't handle
someone like Sung Hee by himself.
For now...
I just need your support.
Ah Jin, look at me.
You know I read the room fast
because I live with beatings.
Ah Jin, you said you needed me.
You're smart.
I know you've
already worked out a plan.
Tell me.
What do you want me to do?
Guys, hurry and pay
the wedding fund for our teacher.
You?
- Hey.
- It's 5,000 won.
I heard Ah Jin and Sung Hee
grabbed each other's hair
in the cafeteria yesterday.
- Really?
- No, they didn't fight.
Sung Hee suddenly poured
strawberry milk on her lunch tray.
- Strawberry milk?
- Is she crazy?
- I'll pay now.
- Ah Jin.
I don't think you need to pay.
Why not?
We have enough collected, and...
Is it because of the rumor?
- That I'm an orphan?
- No.
That's not why.
Do you know who started that rumor?
Seriously?
What's with that response?
Is there something wrong?
No, it's just random that you two
started dating so suddenly.
He still wants to date you,
knowing you poured milk on Ah Jin?
I didn't pour it.
I spilled it by mistake.
Not a drop hit her face.
Anyway
don't bring up her name
in front of me again.
See you.
What's up with her?
She was always dying
to badmouth Ah Jin.
Nice.
How are things with Jun Seo?
You scared me.
You two looked cute together.
So what?
I'm happy for you. He's a good guy.
BOSS
PASSCODE 1004
FRIDAY, 4TH PERIOD, PE
Her passcode reads as "angel"?
That crazy Sung Hee has no shame.
Unbelievable.
FRIDAY
4TH PERIOD, PE
Jun Seo.
I booked the movie for the weekend.
Thanks.
I hate PE.
It's hot and sweaty.
I wish we could just do self-study.
If you hate it so much,
why don't we skip and hang out?
Tell the teacher you're going
to the nurse's office like Ah Jin did
and come to the classroom quietly.
Don't tell anyone.
Okay.
- Excuse me, sir.
- What's up, Sung Hee?
I have a terrible stomachache.
I also feel nauseous.
You can't hold it?
I tried, but I just couldn't.
I think I should get some medicine
at the nurse's office.
Okay. Go on. You can go alone, right?
Yes.
Okay, I'll drop by
with Seon Hui this weekend.
Got it.
Take care, sir.
Bye.
You always take calls here.
I heard your voice
on the way to the nurse's office.
Are you feeling unwell?
I feel a little under the weather.
I see.
Get going, then.
If you're free
could we talk for a moment?
COME TO THE ART ROOM
MAKE SURE TO ERASE THIS
SIM SUNG HEE
This girl.
Sim Sung Hee just left the classroom.
Ah Jin.
Do we have to wait longer?
Sorry, I'm a bit nervous.
Just feel free to tell me. It's fine.
Could...
Could you hold my hand?
Your hand?
My hands shake when I get nervous.
I know you've been
looking out for me.
So, I also thought a lot about it.
About what you told me before.
True Love.
No freaking way.
Back then
I was looking out for you.
Now, I understand your feelings.
"Your feelings"?
I was afraid my friends would
find out, so I tried to deny it.
But I've been regretting it.
It must have been hard for you
to tell me first.
No.
I just want you to--
I'll do whatever you ask.
I think I'm ready now.
Thanks for the help.
It would have taken forever
by myself.
Don't mention it.
It's not a big deal.
The bell's about to ring.
Let's head in.
But I'm not sure if it's all right.
What do you mean?
Didn't we finish the equipment check?
It's not that.
You know I'm on duty today.
I was going to lock up our classroom
but I couldn't find the padlock,
so I just left.
You know our class is extra sensitive
because it's been broken into
a few times.
Should you be announcing that?
What?
If our room actually gets robbed
isn't it partly on you
for not locking it?
If we never catch the person,
like last time
the classmates might blame you.
You never know.
Better safe than sorry.
Man, it's hot.
Changing out of PE gear
is such a hassle.
Dude, you stink.
Sung Hee, didn't you go to the nurse?
What happened to my desk?
Someone went through it.
You didn't do it?
Where's the envelope?
- The envelope.
- What's wrong?
The envelope's gone.
No way. I'm sure
you put it somewhere else.
No, I didn't.
I tucked it in my notebook.
I always keep it there.
It was there before PE for sure.
Sung Hee.
Why were you alone in the classroom?
I wasn't feeling well,
so I got some rest.
How did you open the door?
It was already unlocked.
I definitely locked it.
He says he locked it!
You should have gone to the nurse
if you were sick.
- Why rest here?
- Exactly.
Didn't she tell the PE teacher
she was going to the nurse?
Sung Hee, just answer me straight.
- Did you steal it?
- Goddamn it.
Are you being serious right now?
What if there's nothing in my bag?
Then what?
What if there's nothing?
Then, I won't let it slide.
Here.
Look for yourself.
Is it there?
Take a look.
- Hey.
- There's no envelope.
We haven't checked her locker yet.
You even put a padlock.
Is there something important?
Important? There's nothing.
Don't violate my privacy.
Privacy, huh?
Isn't this my phone?
I was keeping it safe
after you lost it.
But you never came to school,
so I couldn't give it to you.
Then, what about this?
Aren't these the class rep's AirPods
and the cash envelope?
- Is this for real?
- So creepy.
Sung Hee, do you still deny it?
It wasn't me.
I swear!
I've got no reason to steal them!
It's not like my family's poor.
You used to steal in middle school
due to your klepto episodes.
- Seriously?
- No way.
Shouldn't we call the police?
- She's nuts.
- That's crazy.
Don't cry. It's not over yet.
Baek Ah Jin!
I got caught in her trap!
What the hell?
She's worse trash than I am.
You all need to know
what she really is!
Kim Jae Oh's ledger?
The real owner is her.
It was all her, you fucking idiots!
What are you talking about?
Hey.
That ledger's mine.
Who says it's hers?
Do you have proof?
I saw the texts on your phone.
Stuff about collections with a boss,
with the kids' names listed!
Do you think we're close enough
to text each other?
I saw it, damn it.
Here.
Where are these texts, then?
MESSAGES
Why?
If it were true,
shouldn't they be on this phone?
But this is my first time
touching my phone
since you stole it.
Fuck, it's starting to piss me off.
You stole my phone
and snooped through my messages?
That bitch is in a relationship
with the art teacher.
I saw it.
I really did.
They were holding hands.
They were talking about true love.
It was quite a show.
Sim Sung Hee!
Ma'am.
Watch your mouth.
What a psycho.
I'll tell you a secret, too.
Do you know
who our homeroom teacher is marrying?
It's the art teacher.
How dare you speak of such a thing?
Calm down, please.
Ah Jin, you explain.
What is this about?
The art teacher was really worried
about me and suggested counseling.
He introduced me
to the True Love Counseling Center.
- She must have heard that.
- What a liar.
You heard that and claimed
that they were in a relationship
and caused this scene?
Also, did you really steal all these?
Answer me!
No, I didn't!
You were the only one
in the classroom during PE.
Why were you here alone
if you had no reason to steal?
I heard you told the PE teacher
you were going to the nurse!
That's...
I was supposed to meet Jun Seo.
Yoon Jun Seo.
Is this true?
I was in the equipment room
the whole time with the PE captain.
He was.
How could you do this to me?
How could you do this to me, Jun Seo?
I warned you
to quit messing with Ah Jin.
That's it, Sung Hee.
Come with me.
Now!
I'm not going!
- That was epic.
- I know, right?
- Should we post this online?
- Post it.
Aren't these the class rep's AirPods
and the cash envelope?
I swear!
I've got no reason to steal them!
It's not like my family's poor.
You used to steal in middle school
due to your klepto episodes.
THE TRUTH OF SIM SUNG HEE,
ATTORNEY SIM GEUN SEOP'S DAUGHTER
SHE TRIED TO GET ALONG WITH HER
CLASSMATES UNLIKE IN MIDDLE SCHOOL
SIM GEUN SEOP
WORRY ABOUT YOUR OWN FAMILY
THE TRUTH OF SIM GEUN SEOP'S DAUGHTER
COMPLETE
LEGAL CONSULTING PROFESSIONALS
WORRY ABOUT YOUR OWN FAMILY
THE TRUTH OF SIM GEUN SEOP'S DAUGHTER
YOU DON'T GET TO CRITICIZE CRIMINALS
TEACH YOUR DAUGHTER
SOME DECENCY FIRST
STILL GOING TO PRACTICE LAW
AFTER THIS?
She's not my child!
How could you do this to me?
Did you have fun with that woman?
"Have fun"?
Keep your dignity, okay?
"Dignity"?
Keep some dignity for yourself!
Did you sleep with her?
- Leaving early?
- What?
Get out of my face.
I told you.
In movies, the clueless ones
like you always die first.
Shut up, you bitch.
Because of you--
Don't say it's because of me.
This is all on you.
You touched my stuff
poured water on me
and even trashed my lunch tray.
But I let it all slide.
Do you think I don't know
that you framed me as a thief?
If you had been a bit less stupid
this might have gone differently.
What?
Do you honestly think
that handwriting on the board
was Jun Seo's?
At this point,
it doesn't matter who wrote it.
What matters is
that no one will listen to you
that no one will believe you...
and that no one will like you.
You psycho freak.
You never once doubted Jun Seo?
Did you genuinely think
he was into you?
In your dreams, Sung Hee.
That's why
you should have known your limits.
Fighting me only hurts you.
I've got powerful parents.
And you don't.
Since you're an orphan.
Fuck.
- You think I'll let this slide?
- Sung Hee.
Who do you think
Ms. Kwak had an affair with?
That Ms. Kwak.
She got fired,
and all that cash went to waste.
Who did she get caught
cheating with, anyway?
She said she needed legal help,
so even your dad had to step in.
Did you like my gift?
Once your father gets branded
as an adulterous lawyer...
even his law firm won't protect him.
His reputation will be tainted
and you'll become the thief daughter
of an adulterous lawyer.
Will your parents still stand
behind you when that happens?
Can you live with that label
for the rest of your life?
You really thought
you could beat me, didn't you?
You can't, Sung Hee.
As you said
I'm practically an orphan.
But it's not like I was born
without parents.
Help...
I just remember her as my first X.
LIM SUN YE: HER FIRST X
Sung Hee.
Thank you for being my target.
Truly.
You made school life
so much less boring.
What do I think of Baek Ah Jin?
Her acting has
always been exceptional.
She switched masks
whenever it suited her needs.
She's a devil.
A devil
wearing human skin.
DEAR X
Subtitles by Ho Young Yun